{"data":[{"question":"Experiments in the sonic imaging of moving objects ________ in both the United States and Europe well before the Second World War.","a":"were conducting","b":"have been conducted","c":"had been conducted","d":"being conducted","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. It can also show that something happened before a specific time in the past (before the Second World War).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"________ billions and billions of stars exist in the vast space beyond our Milky Way galaxy.","a":"That is estimated","b":"An estimate that","c":"That the estimate","d":"It is estimated that","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Active: People\/ They + think\/ say\/ suppose\/ believe\/ consider\/ report ... + THAT + clause.\u00a0\n- Passive : IT'S + thought\/ said\/ supposed\/ believed\/ considered\/ reported ... + THAT + clause.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"________ gene-bearing bodies within the nuclei of living organisms.","a":"Chromosomes","b":"Chromosomes that are","c":"Chromosomes are","d":"Chromosomes while they are","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- This sentence is a single clause- doesn't need a relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Abner Doubleday, ________, was credited with the invention of baseball in 1839.","a":"who become a Union army general","b":"which became a Union army general","c":"who were a Union army general","d":"a Union army general","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Use a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence to set off clauses, phrases, and words that are not essential to the meaning of the sentence.\u00a0\n- Do not use commas to set off essential elements of the sentence, such as clauses beginning with that (relative clauses).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"________ photosynthesis were to stop, life would disappear from the planet Earth relatively quickly.","a":"For","b":"However","c":"If","d":"Although","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 2: If + past simple, S + would\/should + V.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Each fiber in the bundle ________ only a tiny fraction of the total image.","a":"transmit","b":"transmitted","c":"transmits","d":"to transmit","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- Subject (Each fiber in the bundle) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Antonio Gaudi, architect of Barcelona's Holy Family Church, died before seeing ________ the structure.","a":"on completion of","b":"the completion of","c":"completing of","d":"their completing of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- See something.\u00a0\n- Subject is \" Antonio Gaudi\"- their is not correct.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"This is the factory ________ at work.","a":"they are","b":"where they are","c":"where are","d":"in where they are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- What\/where\/ which... can be use as a relative pronoun. Relative pronouns introduce relative clauses, which are a type of dependent clause.\u00a0\n- Dependent clause followed by relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which\/where...) is narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- Where= in which.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"America's first globe maker was James Wilson, who ________ and blacksmith in his earlier life.","a":"a farmer had been","b":"had been a farmer","c":"farming","d":"being a farmer","answer":"2","explain":"\n- What\/where\/ which... can be use as a relative pronoun. Relative pronouns introduce relative clauses, which are a type of dependent clause.\u00a0\n- Dependent clause followed by relative pronoun (who\/whom\/which\/where...) is narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Napoleon ________ the West Indian island of Santo Domingo in 1801.","a":"attacked","b":"is attacking","c":"has attracted","d":"attacking","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (in 1801).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}